# Marquis Whaley

# UI Visual Designer

■ marquiswhaley@gmail.com □ (904)450-3256 ■ linkedin.com/in/marquiswhaley ■ mrqs.design

#### **SUMMARY**

Hi, my name is Marquis Whaley, I am a UX designer proficient in Adobe design programs, Sketch, and Figma. I have 10 years of experience in Adobe design programs, which allowed me to develop my Photography, Design, and Content Creation skills. I also have a strong background/interest in Digital Photography.

#### **SKILLS**

Tools & Technologies: Adobe Creative Cloud, Microsoft Office, PowerPoint, Figma (Software), Sketch, UsabilityHub, Beautiful.ai, Webflow, , Prototyping, InVision, Procreate App, Capture One, Mailchimp, Google Analytics, Google Ads, Facebook ads, Pixel, Squarespace, Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Tiktok, LinkedIn, Adobe Photoshop

Techniques: team collaboration, user personas, SWOT analysis, user research, user testing, user stories, branding, prototyping, mock-ups, competitive analysis, graphic design, search engine optimization (SEO),

# **PROJECTS**

## Atlasso | Work in Progress

Role: Lead Designer

- Atlasso is a geolocating app that is designed to help metropolitan transit riders reach their bus on time and get to their destination as quickly as possible.
- Researched, designed, and prototyped a bus finder that specifically helps users know the status of busses and find the nearest bus stops at their convenience.
- Tools: Figma, Beautiful.ai, Google Forms, Zoom, Slack

## Rarety | Work in Progress

Role: Lead Designer

- Rarety is a sustainable fashion-focused e-commerce platform for the trendy scavenger.
- Researches, designed and prototyped an aesthetically pleasing yet intuitive e-commerce platform the Millenials and Gen-Z would use to discover vintage and rare finds.
- Tools: Figma, Adobe Design Programs, Beautiful.ai, Typeform, Slack, Zoom

#### EXPERIENCE

### Stylist Assistant

### Slate Studios & Moda Operandi, Inc Nov 2016 - July 2020, Greater New York City Area

 Prepared domestic and fashion products, including steaming, ironing, pinning, sewing, folding, stuffing, and tailoring for use in E-comm photography.

#### Media Production Photography

## Sony Pictures Entertainment Oct 2019 - Dec 2019, Greater New York City Area

- Captured production stills for The Dr. Oz Show marketing department while taping segments.
- · Entered copyright information, metadata requirements, and archived images up to company standards for ease of use.
- · Met production time frames for uploading images.

## Marketing Strategist/Social Media Manager

#### WP Lavori May 2015 - July 2016, Greater New York City Area

- Produced product and promotional photography for both marketing and e-commerce
- Managed and cultivated social media pages that kept customers engaged with the brand
- Organized company events for collection launches, anniversary soirées, and partnership collaborations
- \*For a complete list of recent work experience please check LinkedIn

# **EDUCATION**

# Certificate, UI/UX

#### Thinkful | New York, NY

- Learn industry best practices for User Experience and User Interface design with a focus on visual design.
- Relevant programs: Figma, Miro, Notion, Slack, Sketch, Adobe Design programs

Undergraduate Coursework in, Marketing, General Studies

Florida Atlantic University | Boca Raton, FL